{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter8.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "to work",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548387.0798128,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavorare\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "We work",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548404.2240703,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavoriamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Oggi fa brutto.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548399.6804006,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Today, it's bad (weather).\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She takes a walk.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548360.960816,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui/Lei fa un giro a piedi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "-e",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548377.7767751,
            "question": "lui/lei/Lei -ere",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "-o",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548369.2007492,
            "question": "io -ere",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "partano",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548346.1050947,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They leave\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "I leave",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548383.7845716,
            "question": "Given the definition \"parto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavoro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548470.0389574,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I work\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "You order",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548442.223197,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ordini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi vivete in campagna.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548425.89593,
            "question": "Y'all live in the country.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all make a good impression.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548461.2872376,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi fate bella figura.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She/You(formal) takes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548410.7280257,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prende\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She/You(formal) leave",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548432.4391334,
            "question": "Given the definition \"parte\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She/You(formal) orders",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548448.5034907,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ordina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548436.3752677,
            "question": "I order",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548588.6690447,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You take\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "parti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548590.988835,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You leave\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi fate bella figura.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548502.125805,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all make a good impression.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro vivono in citta'.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548517.0620332,
            "question": "They live in town.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "-iamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548475.0870266,
            "question": "noi -ire",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "They leave",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548597.444037,
            "question": "Given the definition \"partano\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all leave",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548571.3010204,
            "question": "Given the definition \"partite\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Io faccio la spesa al centro commerciale.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548585.1891503,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I do the shopping at the mall.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro vivono in campagna.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457548677.5717225,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They live in the countryside.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavorate",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548686.003857,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all work\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "You leave",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548669.2118118,
            "question": "Given the definition \"parti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "You take",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548664.4677753,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "-ate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548652.2280564,
            "question": "voi -are",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "-ete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548647.8362849,
            "question": "voi -ere",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi viviamo in citta'.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548629.1156235,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We live in town.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavorano",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457548689.6674926,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They work\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "They make friends.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548715.2032745,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro fanno amicizia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "parte",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548771.7620733,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You(formal) leaves\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all leave by bus.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548779.3868155,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi partite in autobus.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavorare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548789.1624331,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to work\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro lavorano la mattina.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548765.35472,
            "question": "They work in the morning.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendono",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457548786.2903948,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They take\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "We work in the morning.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548745.5952365,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi lavoriamo la mattina.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "-o",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548736.0430572,
            "question": "io -ire",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548812.7615614,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You order\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "parti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457548818.473944,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You leave\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "-ono",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1457548794.8023498,
            "question": "loro -ire",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro partono in macchina.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1457548871.1296852,
            "question": "They leave by car.",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavori",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1457548816.577284,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You work\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendete",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457548799.6582532,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all take\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all work",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457548809.4181173,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavorate\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "They work",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457548804.7535777,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavorano\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lui/Lei fa un giro a piedi.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1457549016.1918478,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She takes a walk.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "parte",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457548958.5999327,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You(formal) leave\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi lavarate il pomeriggio.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457548943.8961816,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all work in the afternoon.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavora",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457549005.3278956,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You(formal) work\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "-i",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457548961.7439077,
            "question": "tu -ire",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi facciamo attenzione.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457548951.960466,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We pay attention.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lei fa colazione al bar.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457548893.5444112,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (formal) have breakfast at the cafe.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457548880.489168,
            "question": "I take",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all take",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549064.813469,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendete\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi lavoriamo la mattina.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457549119.5337522,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We work in the morning.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Che tempo fa?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457549124.9336596,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"What's the weather like?\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tu fai ginnastica all'aperto.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549111.294211,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You exercise outdoors.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She/You(formal) work",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549043.0232394,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavora\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "-ono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549035.5989413,
            "question": "loro -ere",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi partite in autobus.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549090.5577202,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all leave by bus.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "They take",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549095.6777968,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "prende",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549144.7493207,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You(formal) takes\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi lavoriamo la sera.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457549210.4283378,
            "question": "We work in the evening.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi vivete in periferia.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549184.836426,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all live in the suburbs.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "to live",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549172.5648694,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vivere\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "What's the weather like?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549151.509506,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Che tempo fa?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi partiamo in treno.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549194.3805144,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We leave by train.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "ordina",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549199.836424,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You(formal) orders\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all live in the suburbs.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549217.1238182,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi vivete in periferia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "You leave",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549259.8112283,
            "question": "Given the definition \"parti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "partite",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549306.2981493,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all leave\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro lavorano la sera.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549325.545425,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They work in the evening.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "-e",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549302.0098646,
            "question": "lui/lei/Lei -ire",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "He/She/You(formal) leaves",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549232.3638275,
            "question": "Given the definition \"parte\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "partire",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549255.5392468,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to leave\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I work",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549263.0832846,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavoro\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "I do the shopping at the mall.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549312.5463958,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io faccio la spesa al centro commerciale.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's hot.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549402.1362472,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Fa caldo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "-i",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549404.577674,
            "question": "tu -are",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro fanno amicizia.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549345.4733093,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They make friends.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi viviamo in campagna.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549418.0477543,
            "question": "We live in the country.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "parto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549348.1851742,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I leave\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "to make, to do",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549422.1448827,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fare\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "You (formal) have breakfast at the cafe.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549364.2014003,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei fa colazione al bar.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Oggi fa bello.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549395.1848571,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Today, it's nice (weather).\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "-iamo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549451.8567061,
            "question": "noi -ere",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "to leave",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457549477.5442376,
            "question": "Given the definition \"partire\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "vivere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549473.7762563,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to live\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "-a",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549448.95254,
            "question": "lui/lei/Lei -are",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi partite in treno.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549460.9204917,
            "question": "Y'all leave by train.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "-o",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549424.64826,
            "question": "io -are",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549470.3443835,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We take\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Today, it's nice (weather).",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549432.440564,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Oggi fa bello.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "partiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549497.9683597,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We leave\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "-iamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549510.3199837,
            "question": "noi -are",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Fa caldo.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549480.7762597,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"It's hot.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "They work in the evening.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549507.471804,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro lavorano la sera.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Fa freddo.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549501.30353,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"It's cold.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "You exercise outdoors.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549487.6322281,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu fai ginnastica all'aperto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "parto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549512.4562354,
            "question": "I leave",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "We leave by train.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549494.4713795,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi partiamo in treno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "-ite",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1457549557.9913824,
            "question": "voi -ire",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "You work",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549550.2622435,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lavori\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "-ano",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549528.0077276,
            "question": "loro -are",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "-i",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549519.191765,
            "question": "tu -ere",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all work in the afternoon.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549544.566872,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi lavarate il pomeriggio.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "We take",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549524.3357584,
            "question": "Given the definition \"prendiamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's cold.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549516.431924,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Fa freddo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Today, it's bad (weather).",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549536.2238877,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Oggi fa brutto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "They live in the countryside.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549567.1035964,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro vivono in campagna.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "We leave",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549582.3274992,
            "question": "Given the definition \"partiamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "We pay attention.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549571.4633403,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi facciamo attenzione.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549577.726723,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to make, to do\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "We live in town.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549592.5352042,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi viviamo in citta'.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavoriamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1457549574.9990258,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We work\"?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}